<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cv_app_Tomas_Skarnulis</string>
    <string name="about_me_item_five_text">I think I have enough potential to be useful for you. If you invested in me, I can promise to do my best, stay and grow with you.</string>
    <string name="about_me_item_five_title">What I can OFFER</string>
    <string name="nav_experience">Experience</string>
    <string name="nav_header_second_text">Android Applications Developer</string>
    <string name="nav_knowledge">Knowledge</string>
    <string name="nav_phone_number">Phone Number</string>
    <string name="title_activity_knowledge">Knowledge</string>
    <string name="info_email">My Email:</string>
    <string name="unity_frag_explain">I use Unity quite rarely, but I enjoy making games with it. I know how animations work, what are coliders. I know how to write scripts and basically make the game work. \n \t * I have done one app with full Google Games Service \n \t * Also I have worked with Vuforia plugin and made fun VR shooter game \n \t * Of course, like many developers I love creating new games</string>
    <string name="unity_frag_subtitle">Experience: about 9 months. Made games: 4 (one is fully available in Google Play Store)</string>
    <string name="visual_frag_explain">"I have some knowledge of it because C# was my first Object Oriented programming language. I enjoy using Visual Studio as well as this language and I actually find it easy.  \n \t * I have real work experience with it \n \t * I know about:  \n \t    .NET \n \t    ASP.NET \n \t    MVC pattern "</string>
    <string name="visual_frag_subtitle">Experience about 1 year. Made 5 applications (not published, but I could show them in the interview)</string>
    <string name="start_second_question">Where you can find all the information?</string>
    <string name="start_second_explain">You can find everything in the Menu section</string>
    <string name="start_button_open">Open Menu</string>
    <string name="phone_button_end_frag">Call me now</string>
    <string name="nav_about_me">About Me</string>
    <string name="info_phone">My Phone Number:</string>
    <string name="info_facebook">My Fecebook:</string>
    <string name="frag_start">Hello!</string>
    <string name="frag_experience">Experience</string>
    <string name="frag_about_me">About Me</string>
    <string name="facebook_button_end_frag">Add me</string>
    <string name="email_button_end_frag">Write now</string>
    <string name="android_frag_explain">I am using Android Studio about 7 months now. I have made some apps which I can show you during the interview. The Android Studio is my strength and I like to use it very much. I know what layouts, adapters, holders, values files are and not only this. By the way, this app was also made with it.  \n \t * I know how to use gradle  \n \t * I understand why I need manifest  \n \t * I know about different screen adaptation  \n  \t * Now I am interested in learning to use MVVM pattern \n \t * I think about switching to Kotlin one day (I am now still using Java)</string>
    <string name="android_frag_subtitle">Experience: about 7 months.The apps made: more than 10 (fully completed)</string>
    <string name="about_me_item_three_title">My WEAKNESSES</string>
    <string name="about_me_item_four_title">My GOALS</string>
    <string name="title_end_frag">So, do you decided?</string>
    <string name="title_end_toolbar">So...</string>
    <string name="explain_end_frag">"I believe you still have questions for me, so you can contact me with one of methods below: "</string>
    <string name="about_me_item_two_text">I always create some goals that make me to move forward. I’m not scared of trying out something new and unfamiliar. I am not only creating ideas, I am doing it. My strength at developing: create Android applications using Android Studio IDE.</string>
    <string name="about_me_item_two_title">My STRENGTHS</string>
    <string name="font_name_qucksand_bold">Quicksand-Bold.otf</string>
    <string name="font_name_qucksand_reg">Quicksand-Regular.otf</string>
    <string name="action_language" translatable="true">Change language...</string>
    <string name="about_me_item_one_title">What I am DOING right now?</string>
    <string name="about_me_item_six_title">What I EXPECT from you</string>
    <string name="experience_title_two">Studies</string>
    <string name="frags_next">Next</string>
    <string name="frags_previos">Previous</string>
    <string name="start_first_explain">Because I want</string>
    <string name="start_main_question">Why am I writing for you?</string>
    <string name="start_practice">Practice</string>
    <string name="start_work">Work for You</string>
    <string name="nav_contact_text">Contact me</string>
    <string name="nav_email">My Email</string>
    <string name="frag_experience_explain">In this section you can find the information about my experience</string>
    <string name="frag_about_me_explain">In this section you can find the information about me</string>
    <string name="about_me_item_one_text">I am currently studying VIKO EIF Smart Equipment Technologies. In my free time (and not only) I am learning to develop Android applications.</string>
    <string name="about_me_item_three_text">I may seem a little slow but I think this is just a matter of time and experience. I have theoretical knowledge about MVVM, MVC and similar design patterns, but I still have to deal with difficulties implementing them. The weakest part of my knowledge is React Native.</string>
    <string name="about_me_item_four_text">Programming and developing applications is my hobby, so the job where I can do these things would be meaningful time investment to me. I hope to be helpful for you and get the advantages from it myself, so it will be beneficial for both sides. Therefore, my main goal at the moment is a pleasant work, perhaps at your company.</string>
    <string name="about_me_item_six_text">I hope you understand that I am not yet a senior programmer, so I would always appreciate your help. This way we might achieve the perfection.</string>
    <string name="experience_explain_one">I have practiced at the IoT Teltonika Academy. Runtime - 270 hours. I have proof of it (a certificate).</string>
    <string name="experience_explain_two">While studying I have had two internships. I have been learning C# language since. I also have the theoretical knowledge about programming, design templates, program memory, Object Oriented Programing (OOP) and a lot more.</string>
    <string name="experience_explain_three">I have some experience with Google Play Console, App publishing, Updates.</string>
    <string name="experience_explain_four">I have some experience with Google Play Games services. One of the games is already available in Google Play Store</string>
    <string name="github_frag_subtitle">Experience: about 3 months</string>
    <string name="github_frag_explain">I am not using it a lot, because usually I work alone, but I would undoubtedly use an opportunity to work on bigger projects.\n \t* I know how to push or clone projects \n \t* I do not face the difficulties with merging conflicts. \n \t* That is why I believe you could help me with bigger projects....</string>
    <string name="react_frag_subtitle">Experience: about 2 months. This is still quite new to me.</string>
    <string name="react_frag_explain">I am new at this JavaScript framework but I am surely excited to learn it and to know the basic structure of a project. \n \t * I might seems slow, but I get things done \n \t * I know how to use NPM \n \t * I would like to learn it</string>
</resources>

